[{"answer": "I don't wanna mix in everything! My guys don't know your guys. You can't just lock 'em all in the same machine together. They'll start a riot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No. I can't say as I have", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, they tend to give those jobs to e", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I know. Well, okay. Okay. What else do ya like", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "And it's probably a union thing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Talk show host. That's good", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Those unions.  Okay. Sports,...movies. What about a talk show host", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I think I'd be good at that. I talk to people all the time. Someone even told me once they thought I'd be a good talk show host", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, that's where it gets tricky", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What should I do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Go back", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So what? You're entitled", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That's right. You're emotional", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That's right. You're emotional", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Never happened", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't know where you're getting this from. I....you're serious aren't you? Oh,  you see", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "\" I'll always be a winner and you'll always be a loser", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, so that's that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's not that", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Nah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I got a sauce", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Where are you gonna get this mickey? I can't believe I'm saying", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You got a mickey sauce", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I told her what a sexist he is. How he cheats on his wife", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "But she didn't know he doesn't recycle", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Nah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It was about 1200 bucks", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Revenge.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh! That's my friend", "qsentId": 30}]